tristancafe.com 2014-05-28

# Privacy Policy - TristanCafe

TRISTANCAFE.COM fully respects your privacy. In fact, when you register in our social network and forums, only the username, password, and email address are required. Your IP address is also recorded in our database upon registration. This information is used for system administration, social network management and forum moderation, and can also be used to create broad demographic summaries of the countries where our visitors come from. Other information such as name, sex, location, birthday, etc are completely optional. In any case, we absolutely do NOT sell, loan, or otherwise disclose any such personal information to anyone, particularly third parties such as marketers and advertisers. At most, advertisers are presented with only broad statistics such as country demographics of visitors and number of registered members. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

TRISTANCAFE.COM uses cookies to both store and retrieve login information on a user’s system. Cookies are just small text files and have no ability to search through your computer and transmit information about you. They are absolutely NOT adware or spyware. Our 3rd-party advertisers may also use their own cookies when you view or select their advertisement, content or service, and non-personally identifiable information may be collected by them for ad-serving purposes.

Please remember that any personal information that you reveal in our social network, forums or any media that is publicly accessible is not subject to this Privacy Policy and may be seen by third parties not directly related to TRISTANCAFE.COM.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
